Guide to the Stanford Alumni Association Records SC0318
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford Alumni Association records
1893-1987
bulk
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford Alumni Association
SC0318
16 Linear Feet (18 boxes)
This collection Includes minutes, financial records, Executive Board minutes, memos, and other documents (1944-1971), correspondence, questionnaires, class and conference materials, lists, articles, photographs, slides, audio tapes, and memorabilia; a substantial portion of the collection pertains to class reunions, continuing education courses, and career day programs. Correspondents and authors represented include Dorothy M. Ormsby, Ralph W. Hansen, Winston Norman, Archie Rice, and Charles Michael Stanton. Included are background materials (compiled by Prof. Harry Harding) for the SAA Seminars in the People's Republic of China, 1979. Also of note are questionnaires concerning student unrest on campus, 1970, candidates for university president, 1970, and surveys done by the Stanford Associates on student communications and alumni attitudes, 1962-1963.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
The records were received by the Stanford University Archives via administrative transfers, 1985-2001; as well as by gift from Philip Duffy, 1985; the estate of Dorothy Ormsby, 1985; and Barbara Finberg, 2006.
Information about Access
This collection is open for research; materials must be requested at least 48 hours in advance of intended use.
Biographical / Historical
The Stanford Alumni Association was founded in June 1892 by members of Stanford's first graduating class. It was an independent organization until September 1, 1998, when it became a division of the university.
Arrangement
Materials are arranged by accession.
Description of the Collection
The collection includes minutes, financial records, Executive Board minutes, memos, and other documents (1944-1971), correspondence, questionnaires, class and conference materials, lists, articles, photographs, slides, audio tapes, and memorabilia; a substantial portion of the collection pertains to class reunions, continuing education courses, and career day programs. Correspondents and authors represented include Dorothy M. Ormsby, Ralph W. Hansen, Winston Norman, Archie Rice, and Charles Michael Stanton. Included are background materials (compiled by Prof. Harry Harding) for the SAA Seminars in the People's Republic of China, 1979. Also of note are questionnaires concerning student unrest on campus, 1970, candidates for university president, 1970, and surveys done by the Stanford Associates on student communications and alumni attitudes, 1962-1963.
Student movements -- California -- Stanford.; Photoprints.; Universities and colleges -- Alumni; Phonotapes.; Continuing education.; Norman, Winston.; Stanford University. Stanford Associates; Hansen, Ralph W.; Rice, Archie; Stanton, Charles Michael.; Ormsby, Dorothy M.; Stanford Alumni Association; Stanford Alumni Association
- Audiovisual Materials, Accession ARCH-1981-049
  - Reel-to-Reel Audiotapes, Subseries 1
    - Stanford Alumni Conference, various events, May 11, 1962; 7 audiotape reel(s) (Box 1)
    - Speech by Prof. David Faville before the Portland, Oregon Stanford Alumni Meeting, April 24, 1955; 2 audiotape reel(s) (Box 1)
    - Stanford Alumni Roundtable, May 20, 1950; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 1)
    - Stanford class day exercises, June 1963; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 1)
    - W. H. Cowley, "Student Upheavals in Perspective," Campus Conference, 1965; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 1)
    - Alumni lecture, May 22, 1965; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 1)
    - Chinese music, Undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 1)
    - Stanford Alumni Conference: Mr. Dinkelspiel, Alf Brandon, Al Masters, Don Winbigler, Dr. Russel Lee, 1954; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 1)
    - Stanford Alumni Conference: entertainment at luncheon, Dr. Wallace Sterling, 1954; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 1)
    - Dinner for President Sterling, October 10, 1964; 3 audiotape reel(s) (Box 1)
    - Luncheon honoring Mrs. Chandler, November 30, 1971; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 1)
    - Sterling's Alumni Conference spot (sound for film), 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 1)
    - Stanford Today and Tomorrow, a panel discussion from the 1959 Alumni Conference held at Dinkelspiel Auditorium, May 16, 1959; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 1)
    - unlabeled, 3 audiotape reel(s) (Box 1)
  - Film, Subseries 2
    - Alumni Conference TV clip by Dr. Sterling, Undated; 2 film reel(s) (8mm) (Box 1)
  - Slides, Subseries 3
    - 76 color slides, possibly from "Simpson/Hirsch report" regarding Alumni Association activities, 1967 (Box 1)
- Portraits of Stanford Alumni Association Presidents and Officers, Accession ARCH-2001-102
  - Ashley, G. H. (Box 1)
  - Burnhill, Henry Clifford (Box 1)
  - Caughey, Edgar Reginald (Box 1)
  - Classen, Willard J. ["1934-35"] (Box 1)
  - Cleaveland, Newton (Box 1)
  - Crothers, George E. (Box 1)
  - Field, Charles K. ["1946"] (Box 1)
  - Fowler, William Henry Begbie (Box 1)
  - Hamilton, "Bones" (Box 1)
  - Jenness, C. K. ["First President 1892-93"] (Box 1)
  - McElroy, Floyd L. (Box 1)
  - Nourse, J. T. ["1918-19"] (Box 1)
  - Petree, Neil Harold (Box 1)
  - Rearn [?Kearn], Frank (Box 1)
  - Reppy, Roy V. (Box 1)
  - Sloss [Jr.], Leon (Box 1)
  - Unidentified (Box 1)
- Records, Accession ARCH-2001-104
  - Minutes and Other Records, Subseries 1
    - Treasurer's book, 1893-1900 (Box 1)
    - Minute book, 1907-1917 (Box 1)
    - Minute book, 1909 May-1924 Jun (Box 1)
      Scope and Contents note
      Also includes constitution, lists, notices and articles, ballots, reports, correspondence, and resolutions.
    - Class secretary's fund records, 1920-29 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Proposed constitution, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Minutes, Executive Committee, 1924 Sep-1926 Aug (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Minutes, Executive Committee, 1926 Sep-1928 Aug (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Minutes, Executive Committee, 1928 Sep-1931 Jun (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Minutes, Executive Committee, 1931 Sep-June 1933 Jun (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Minutes, Executive Committee, 1933 Sep (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Minutes, Committee of Thirty-Five, 1934 Oct 30 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Minutes, Alumni Council, 1935 Sep-Nov. 1937 Nov (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Minutes, Executive Board, 1938 Apr-1939 May (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Minutes and other records, Executive Board, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Alumni Assembly, May 15, 1948 - information on delegates (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Alumni Assembly, May 14, 1949 - information on delegates (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Records 1957-60: committee précis (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Records 1957-60: survey letters (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Records 1957-60: references, statistics, history (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Records 1957-60: development steering committee, committee meetings, by-laws, board enlargement (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Records 1957-60: Associates' history (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Minutes, Executive Board, 1958-1959 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Records, 1958-59: summer camp (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Records, 1958-59: publications (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Records, 1958-59: membership (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Records, 1958-59: long range planning (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Records, 1958-59: finance and operations (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Records, 1958-59: conferences (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Records, 1958-59: clubs (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Records, 1958-59: class and reunions (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Records, 1958-59: Bowman Alumni House (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Records, 1958-59: admissions (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Records, 1958-59: general (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Trustee election, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Trustee election, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Trustee election, special appointment, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Trustee election, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Trustee election, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Trustee election, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Trustee election, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Trustee election, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Trustee election, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Trustee election, general information, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Trustee election, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Trustee election (historical) (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Hoover Medal Award nominees A-D, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Hoover Medal Award nominees G-H, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Hoover Medal Award nominees J-W, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Hoover Medal Award, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Hoover Medal Award, basic information (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Hoover Medal Award, maker of the die in Brussels (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Hoover Medal Award, printed material (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Hoover Medal Award, nominations, 1967-1981 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Hoover Medal Award, nominees, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Hoover Medal Award, presentation, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Alumni Club Manual 1940 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Preliminary presentation of the campus secretary's job to the alumni executive board, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Report of the Student Financial Manager, Alfred S. Nelson, 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Stanford Sierra Camp - book collection in honor of Robert R. Hind (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous materials (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Form Letters and Communications, Subseries 2
    - Form letters, 1911-1916 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Form letters, 1917-1920 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Form letters, 1921-1923 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Form letters, 1924-1926 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Form letters, 1927-1929 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Form letters, 1930-1932 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Form letters, 1933-1936 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Form letters, miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Letters to alumni clubs and officers, 1922-1925 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Letters to alumni clubs and officers, 1926-1929 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Letters to alumni clubs and officers, 1930-1935 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Letters to alumni clubs and officers, miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Sample organizational forms (Box 6)
    - SAA constitution, election notices, ballot forms (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Subscription forms, change of address, etc. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Advertising rates and solicitations (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Forms re "Ten Year Book" and "Stanford and the War" (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Events (Notices, Mailings, Programs, etc.), Subseries 3
    - Alumni Lecture Series (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Founders Day (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Alumni luncheons (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - University Day and Reunions (Box 6, Folder 10-12)
    - Alumni conferences (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Football, shows, dinners, and dances (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Stanford Associates, Subseries 4
    - Communications Committee, survey on alumni attitudes, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Communications Committee, survey of alumni attitudes, involvement and giving, 1963 Nov 8 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Communications Committee, agenda and materials for meeting of Nov. 16, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Communications Committee, "Student Communications at Stanford" by Richard F. Carter and George Comstock, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Oversize Items, Subseries 5
    - Bowman House guest book, 1952-1964 (Box 8)
    - Ledger of miscellaneous records (mostly statistical, not financial), 1932-1949 (Box 8)
    - Scrapbook, 1939-1940 (Box 8)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2002-051
  - Stanford Alumni Conference, programs, 1937-1942 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Alumni Conference, programs, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Alumni Conference, programs, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Alumni Conference, Portland, press releases and bios on speakers, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Stanford Alumni Conference, program, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - S. U. press releases re Stanford Alumni Conference, 1949, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2002-292
  - SAA Continuing Studies programs, 1975-1981 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Travel/Study programs, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Hudson Bay College - expedition notebook and "Log of Arctic and Hudson Bay College August 6 to 22, 1988" compiled by Dennis Puleston (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous programs and notices (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2005-055
  - Executive Board minutes 1944, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Executive Board minutes and memos, 1955-1959 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Executive Board minutes and memos, 1960 Feb-1961 Apr (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Executive Board minutes and memos, 1961 Jun-Sep (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Executive Board minutes and memos, 1962-1964 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Executive Board 1966-1967 - General (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Executive Board 1966-1967 - Agenda and minutes (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Executive Board 1966-1967 - Awards / Classes & Reunions (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Executive Board 1966-1967 - Clubs (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Executive Board 1966-1967 - Conferences / Finance and Operations (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Executive Board 1966-1967 - Membership / Program Analysis (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Executive Board 1966-1967 - Publications / Sierra Camp (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Executive Board Agenda and Documents, October 1967 meeting (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Executive Board Agenda and Documents, March 1968 meeting (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Executive Board Agenda and Documents, May 1968 meeting (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Executive Board Agenda and Documents, October 1968 meeting (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Executive Board White Book, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Financial Statement Year Ended October 31. 1968 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Executive Board Agenda and Documents, February 1969 meeting (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Executive Board Agenda and Documents, May 1969 meeting (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Executive Board Agenda and Documents, October 1969 meeting (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Executive Board White Book, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Executive Board Agenda and Documents, February 1970 meeting (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Executive Board Agenda and Documents, February 1971 meeting (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Alumni Advisory Board minutes (re legacy admissions), circa 1933 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Alumni Association of Japan, minutes, 1946-1947 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Alumni Athletic Advisory Committee, minutes, 1945 Oct 8 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Conference Committee, minutes, 1939 Dec 11 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2005-257
  - Record book containing constitution and minutes, 1892-1905 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Typed minutes: 1906 March 9 and 1907 March 6, and typed report: 1905 May 23 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Typed text: WES Remarks, Founders' Day, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Relates history of SAA based on minutes in record book in folder 1.
  - Address delivered before annual meeting by Doremus A. Hayes, 1893 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Address delivered before annual meeting by F. L. Burk, 1894 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Addresses delivered before annual meeting by George H. Ashley, Arthur H. Barnhisel, and Jessica Washburn, 1895 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Addresses delivered before annual meeting by Clarke B. Whittier and Cora Millicent Palmer, 1897 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Addresses delivered before annual meeting by Jefferson Elmore and Charles J. C. Bennett, 1898 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2006-052
  - China Seminar 1979 background materials: introduction and travel tips (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Includes Paul A. Cohen's Report on the Visit of the Young Political. Leaders Delegation to the People's Republic of China, 1977
  - China Seminar 1979 background materials: traditional China and contemporary China (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - China Seminar 1979 background materials: Chinese foreign relations (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Includes Harry Harding's "Chinese Foreign Policy in the Post-Mao Era"
  - China Seminar 1979 background materials: Chinese domestic policy (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - China Seminar 1979 background materials: Chinese foreign policy and addenda (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Original 3-ring binder (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2007-037
  - Stanford Alumni Association Executive Board agenda, minutes, and documents for the following meetings: October 1971, June 1971, February 1971, September 1970, and February 1969 (each meeting bound together) (Box 1)
    These booklets were prepared for Kenneth Cuthbertson.
- Travel/Study records, ARCH-2016-090
  - Photographs
    - Faces of Melanesia - Fiji, Vanuatu, Solomon Islands & Papua New Guinea #1, April 24- May 12, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Faces of Melanesia - Fiji, Vanuatu, Solomon Islands & Papua New Guinea #2, April 24- May 12, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Antarctica, South Georgia, and the Falkland Islands, Jan 4-24, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Ultimate Seychelles with Aldabra Atoll, Jan 6-23, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Stanford Overseas Studies Program, 2000 - 2005 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Stanford Overseas Studies Program, 2000 - 2005 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Rainforests and Reefs, Jan 10-24, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Ultimate Seychelles Expedition, Mar 16-31, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Circumnavigation of the Black Sea, Jun 7-21, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Circumnavigation of the Black Sea, Jun 7-21, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Circumnavigation of New Guinea - Voyage I: Port Moresby to Wewak, Mar 7-22, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Circumnavigation of New Guinea - Voyage I: Port Moresby to Wewak, Mar 7-22, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Bay of Bengal & The Andaman Sea, Jan 17 - Feb 6 2011 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Around the World 2002 (photo album) (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Around the World 2002 (photo album) (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Sanctuaries of the Ancient World (Feb 20 - Mar15, 2003) (empty album) (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Nomads of the North (2004) (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Sacred Places and Ancient People, 0 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Stanford Millennium College, 0 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Group Photos/ Faculty Photos, 0 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Stanford Around the World College, 1996 Jan 19 - Feb 14 (Box 2)
    - South America Expedition by Private Jet, 1998 Mar 2-21 (Box 2)
  - Guides
    - The Log of Anatolia's Ancient Seacoast Cruise, Oct 16 - Nov 2, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - The Log of Stanford College in Antarctica, Dec 27, 1986 - Jan 12, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Stanford Alumni Association - 1987 College in Antarctica, Jun-1905 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Spice Islands and Borneo College - Biak, Irian Jaya to Brunei - Expedition Log, Apr 27 - May 9, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Spice Islands and Borneo College - Biak to Brunei - Expedition Notebook, Apr 24 - May 10, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Stanford Expedition Cruises - Iberian Coast & Rivers of France, Jun 5 - 18, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - The Log of 1988 College in Baja California and The Sea of Cortez, Mar 19 - 30, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Log of Arctic and Hudson Bay College, Aug 6 - 22, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Log of Stanford College in British Isles, Jun 10 - 26, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Log of Stanford Voyage to the Sea of Cortez - Cruise SL18, Dec 7 - 14, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Guatemala Log, 0 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - North Pole Voyage 1992 - Sovetskiy Soyuz, July 5 - 22, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Expedition Log - Stanford College in ANTARCTICA The Falkland Islands and South Georgia. Aboard the World Discoverer, Ja 9 - 27, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - A Voyage to the Lands of Humboldt and Darwin - Aboard the World Discoverer, 21 Oct - 7 Nov 1994 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Stanford Alumni Association - Northwest Passage Expedition, Sep 1-17 1994 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - 1994 Baja Whale Watching Expedition, Mar 14 - 25, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Fabled Islands of the Indian Ocean - Voyage from Seychelles to Madagascar - On board M.S. Caledonian Star, Feb 12 - 24, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - A Suitcase Seminar in Patagonia, Oct 28 - Nov 11, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Polynesia Under Sail - Aboard the Wind Song, Oct 10 - 21, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Baja Whale Watching Expedition - Aboard M.V. Sea Lion, Mar 6 - 14, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Sacred Places & Ancient Peoples Expedition - Aboard Explorer II, Feb 1 - 17, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Log of Bhutan and the Bay of Bengal College - Aboard Sea Goddess II, Feb 15 - Mar 6, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Exploring Alaska's Coastal Wilderness, Aug 20 - 27, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Pre-Departure Notes: Faces of Melanesia, Oct 13 - 20, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Expedition Log: Faces of Melanesia, Oct 13 - 20, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Pre-Departure Notes: Fire & Ice: Islands of North Pacific, May 24 - Jun 13, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Expedition Log: Fire & Ice Islands of North Pacific, May 24 - Jun 13, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - 2000 Unseen Japan - suitcase seminar (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - 2001 Stanford Amazon Expedition - The Greatest Voyage in Natural History (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Among the Great Whales, Mar 17 - 25, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Expedition Log: Antarctica, South Georgia, The Falkland Islands, Jan 9 - 29, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Among The Great Whales - Aboard the M.V. Sea Lion, Mar 17 - 25, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Baja California - Among the Great Whales, Mar 9 - 16, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Bridging the Bering Strait - expedition log, Jun 9 - 22, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Aegean Family Adventure 2003, Jul 8 - 21, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Expedition Log: Wild Siberia Expedition - Voyage I, Jun 3 - 16, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Expedition Log: Wild Siberia Expedition - Voyage II, Jun 14 - 27, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Pre-departure Notes: Wild Siberia Expeditions, 38504 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Expedition Log: 2004 Tahiti to Fiji College, Oct 30 - Nov 15, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Amazon - The Greatest Voyage in Natural History, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Amazon Expedition - The Greatest Voyage in Natural History, Apr 10 - 18, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Pre-departure Notes: Circumnavigation of New Guinea Expedition, 38777 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Heli-hiking 2006 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Voyage to the Lands of Humboldt & Darwin, 0 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Travel Log: Stanford Around the World College, Jan 19 - Feb 14, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - South America Expedition by Private Jet, Mar 2 - 21, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 46)